donq.com 2019-02-24

# Privacy Policy » Don Q Rum

This Policy covers the Destilería Serrallés, Inc. (“Serrallés”) and www.donq.com (the “Site”) privacy policy regarding type of information that Serrallés may collect from the Site and the treatment of this personal information. This Policy will also provide you with instructions on what to do if you don’t wish to share personal information with Serrallés when you visit our Site. Personal information, for purposes of this privacy policy, is information about you that is personally identifiable including but not limited to your name, age, personal identification information, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available, it also includes any other information voluntarily provided by you. The DonQ.com site is intended only for persons of legal drinking age. Date of birth verification is required at the entrance of the Site. If someone under the legal drinking age has provided us with personal information by obtaining access in violation to the Site access restrictions and its Terms of Use, Serrallés asks that the parent or guardian of that person contact our Consumer Relations Center at [donq.contact@gmail.com](mailto:donq.contact@gmail.com). Upon receiving your request, we will promptly remove such information from our records. This policy only applies to the Site and people that Serrallés employs or manages regarding the administration of the Site.

  * #### 1Information Collection and Use

    1. Serrallés collects personal information when any user accesses the Site.
    2. All personal information provided to Serrallés through the Site is purely voluntary in nature. If you do not want your information to be collected by the Site, please do not submit such information to the Site. If you have already submitted personal information to Serrallés and wish to have such information removed from our records, please contact our Consumer Relations Center at [donq.contact@gmail.com](mailto:donq.contact@gmail.com).
    3. When you contact us we may ask for information such as your name and company’s name (if applicable), address, date of birth, home telephone number, business telephone number, mobile telephone number and any other identifying information which may be required, by Serrallés, from time to time. Once you contact us, you are not anonymous to us.
    4. Serrallés collects information about your transactions with us, including information about your use of the Site, the dates and times you access the Site, the version of the terms of use and privacy policy which you have accepted every time you log on to the Site and any other information, freely provided by you, which Serrallés may choose to collect from time to time.
    5. Serrallés may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Serrallés cookie information, and the page you request.
    6. Serrallés uses information for the following general purposes: fulfill your requests, improve our products or services, for entry into contests and sweepstakes, to send you publications and/or advertisements, to provide to third parties affiliated to Serrallés and to contact you. We will not provide your information to non affiliated third parties without your consent.
    7. By entering personal information into the Site you are acknowledging that you are of legal drinking age in the jurisdiction in which access to the Site was made.
    8. This Privacy Policy was posted on the Site on September 25, 2009 and is effective as of its posting.
    9. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, contact [donq.contact@gmail.com](mailto:donq.contact@gmail.com).
  * #### 2Information Sharing and Disclosure

    * Serrallés does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or organizations except as provided herein, or under the following circumstances:
    1. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
    2. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Serrallés’ Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * #### 3Cookies

    1. Serrallés may set and access Serrallés cookies on your computer.
    2. Serrallés may use web beacons to access Serrallés cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with the Site’s Services.
  * #### 4Changes to this Privacy Policy

    1. Serrallés may update this policy from time to time. Serrallés may provide you with notices, including those regarding changes to the Agreement, by email, regular mail or postings on the Site.
